[lively tropical music]
[活泼的热带音乐]
* *
**
[crowd cheering]
[人群欢呼]
- What you see before you
- 你所看到的
is the culmination
of my lifelong dream.
是顶峰
我一生的梦想。
A place of my own
where I can work out
一个属于我自己的地方
我可以在哪里锻炼
every day, any time I want.
每天，任何我想要的时间。
Larry's Gym!
拉里的健身房！
[all cheering]
[大家欢呼]
[cheering continues]
[欢呼声继续]
[scissors slice]
- Ow!
[剪刀切片]
- 噢！
- Looking out at this sea
- 眺望这片大海
of flaccid muscles
and sagging flesh,
松弛的肌肉
以及下垂的肉，
frankly, I'm disgusted.
坦白说，我很反感。
all:
Aww.
全部：
哇。
- Therefore, I'm opening the gym
- 所以我要开健身房
to everyone in Bikini Bottom.
致比基尼堡的每个人。
all:
Yeah! Whoo-hoo!
全部：
是啊！呼呼！
- For the price
of a lifetime membership.
- 对于价格
终身会员资格。
all:
Aww.
全部：
哇。
- But today, everything is free!
- 但今天，一切都是免费的！
all:
Yeah!
全部：
是啊！
- Shape us and mold us
in your image.
-塑造我们并塑造我们
在你的形象中。
[all cheering]
[大家欢呼]
- You're the lobster, Larry.
- 你是龙虾，拉里。
The alpha lobster.
阿尔法龙虾。
- Well, I don't know
if I'd say that.
- 嗯，我不知道
如果我这么说的话。
- Oh, I filled out
a membership form.
- 哦，我填了
会员表格。
- Ooh.
- 哦。
- Me too.
- 我也是。
- What's in that pink box?
- 那个粉色盒子里装的是什么？
- Uh, doughnuts, sir.
- 呃，甜甜圈，先生。
- "Dough nut"
bring those in here!
- “面团坚果”
把那些带进来！
In the meantime,
enjoy yourself
与此同时，
玩得开心
because your first visit
is free.
因为你第一次来
是免费的。
- Is it true that
everything is free?
- 这是真的吗
一切都是免费的？
- That's right, sir.
- 是的，先生。
For your first visit, we--
对于您的第一次访问，我们——
Hello?
你好？
In conclusion,
I'm at your service
总之，
我随时为您服务
to turn anyone, anyone, into a
rippling heap of muscle glory!
把任何人，任何人，变成
荡漾堆肌肉的荣耀！
- [grunting]
- [咕哝]
- Boy, I've got my work
cut out for me.
- 男孩，我有工作了
为我剪下来。
The doors are automatic.
门是自动的。
Just step on the mat.
只需踩在垫子上即可。
- Oh!
- 哦！
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
- [growls]
Here.
- [咆哮]
在这里。
- Ah, thanks, Larry.
- 啊，谢谢，拉里。
- Ugh.
- 呃。
- [grunting]
- [咕哝]
- Uh, what are you doing?
- 呃，你在做什么？
- You said everything was free.
- 你说一切都是免费的。
- [laughs]
No, no.
- [笑]
不，不。
Your first visit is free.
您的第一次访问是免费的。
- So what you're saying is,
if I never leave,
- 所以你的意思是
如果我永不离开
it'll be free forever!
它将永远免费！
[both laughing]
[两人都笑了]
- Time to go live the dream.
- 是时候实现梦想了。
Right after I file
this paperwork.
就在我提交文件后
这份文书工作。
I didn't think there'd be
so much of it.
我没想到会有
这么多。
- Excuse me, Larry,
I was just working out
- 对不起，拉里，
我刚刚在锻炼
and I was wondering,
is this normal?
我想知道，
这是正常的吗？
- Aah!
- 啊啊！
Even your cramps have cramps.
甚至你的抽筋也有抽筋。
You need to follow
my number one rule:
你需要遵循
我的第一条规则：
always be hydrating.
始终保持保湿。
- Fine.
- 美好的。
[gulping]
[吞咽]
Gee, Larry, you think
I'll ever be as strong as you?
哎呀，拉里，你认为
我会像你一样坚强吗？
- Sure! What kind of
a gym owner would I be
- 当然！什么样的
我会成为健身房老板
if I couldn't take a puny,
squishy, lump like you?
如果我不能承受一点点
像你一样软软的、肿块的？
- [laughs]
Squishy.
- [笑]
软软的。
- What I'm saying is,
I can make you a man.
- 我想说的是，
我可以让你成为一个男人。
- Hooray!
- 万岁！
- I'm gonna make you
my personal project.
- 我会让你
我的个人项目。
Of course, you'll have to sign
up for a lifetime membership.
当然，你得签字
获得终身会员资格。
- I'm ready!
- 我准备好了！
[grunting and groaning]
[咕哝和呻吟]
- That reminds me, you need
to start hydrating right now.
- 这提醒了我，你需要
现在就开始补水。
- [panting]
- [气喘吁吁]
Yes, sir.
是的，先生。
- And remember,
always be hydrating!
- 请记住，
平时要注意保湿！
- Okay, I will.
- 好的，我会的。
- That's what I like to see.
- 这就是我喜欢看到的。
Come on,
we'll finish those later.
来吧，
我们稍后会完成这些。
- Good, 'cause I was
really crashing there,
- 很好，因为我是
真的在那里崩溃了，
signing those papers.
签署这些文件。
"Feeling the burn,"
is that what you call it?
“感觉到灼烧感，”
你就是这么称呼它的吗？
I heard angels singing.
我听到天使在唱歌。
Beautiful angels.
That's normal, right?
美丽的天使。
这很正常，对吧？
- It's Larry!
King of the gym!
- 是拉里！
健身房之王！
[all cheering]
[大家欢呼]
- Oh, you guys.
- 哦，你们。
I'm just an ordinary
alpha lobster doing his job.
我只是一个普通人
阿尔法龙虾正在做他的工作。
Towel boy!
毛巾小子！
Polish this crown
for me, will you?
打磨这顶王冠
为了我，你愿意吗？
- Hey, join us, boy.
- 嘿，加入我们吧，男孩。
Oh, I can't believe
I'm allowed to lift these
哦，我不敢相信
我可以举起这些
really heavy pieces of metal
for free.
非常重的金属件
免费。
[grunting]
Oh.
[咕噜声]
哦。
[gulps]
[吞咽]
Free.
自由的。
- I don't know, Larry.
- 我不知道，拉里。
I'm not good at
lifting things.
我不擅长
举起东西。
Aah! Aah! Ow!
啊啊！啊啊！噢！
Ooh!
[groans]
哦！
[呻吟]
Aah!
啊啊！
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
Ow!
噢！
- Let me see.
- 让我看看。
I may have something
that'll work for you.
我可能有东西
这对你有用。
Here we go.
开始了。
Cotton swabs, cotton balls.
棉签、棉球。
Here, try this on
for size, Hercules.
来，试试这个
对于尺寸，赫拉克勒斯。
- [grunting, groaning]
- [咕哝，呻吟]
Aah!
啊啊！
How am I doing?
我怎么样？
- Pathetic.
- 可怜的。
- Look, Larry, I'm hydrating.
- 拉里，你看，我正在补充水分。
Oh, I am hydrating so much.
哦，我的水分太多了。
- Yeah, I've got another
idea, SpongeBob.
- 是的，我还有另一个
想法，海绵宝宝。
Come with me.
跟我来吧。
First thing tomorrow morning,
明天早上第一件事，
this is gonna be where
I lead my exercise class.
这将是在哪里
我带领我的运动课。
- I'll be there.
- That's the spirit.
- 我会在那里。
- 这就是精神。
And we're going to get you
started early.
我们会找到你
很早就开始了。
Let me see some crunches.
让我看看一些仰卧起坐。
- [crunching loudly]
- [嘎吱嘎吱地响]
- The only thing I want
to see in your mouth
- 我唯一想要的
在你嘴里看到
is that water bottle.
是那个水瓶吗？
Now, what did I tell you?
现在，我告诉你了什么？
Always be hydrating!
平时一定要注意保湿！
Now I'll show you some crunches.
现在我将向您展示一些仰卧起坐。
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
- Oh, I can do that.
- 哦，我能做到。
That's what I do when I laugh.
我笑的时候就是这么做的。
[laughing]
[笑]
Only now I'll do it on my back.
只是现在我会在背上做。
[laughing]
[笑]
- Could you do it
without the laugh?
- 你能做到吗
没有笑声？
- I won't lie to you, Larry.
- 我不会对你撒谎，拉里。
Probably not.
[laughs]
可能不会。
[笑]
- Whatever works, I guess.
- 我想，无论什么有效。
Keep up with that
and most importantly--
跟上那个
最重要的是——
- Always be hydrating.
- 始终保持水分。
[laughing]
[笑]
- [sighs]
Okay.
- [叹气]
好的。
I have a lot of paperwork
to catch up on.
我有很多文书工作
赶上。
- Free towels, free towels!
- 免费毛巾，免费毛巾！
Free towels, free towels!
Free!
免费毛巾，免费毛巾！
自由的！
- Do you have to do that
in front of me?
- 你必须这样做吗
在我面前？
- Yes.
Yes, I do,
- 是的。
是的，我愿意，
because I sincerely
want to thank you
因为我真诚地
想谢谢你
for a truly life-changing
experience.
真正改变生活
经验。
Sucker!
[laughs]
傻瓜！
[笑]
- [groans]
- [呻吟]
- Nice potbelly!
- 好大肚腩！
- Potbelly?
- 大腹便便？
[SpongeBob laughing]
[海绵宝宝大笑]
Oh, I forgot all about
my protégé.
哦，我全忘了
我的门生。
[SpongeBob laughs]
[海绵宝宝笑]
[gasps]
[喘气]
Oh, my Neptune!
哦，我的海王星！
- Again with this!
- I have had it.
- 又是这个！
- 我已经受够了。
- Come on, already.
- What's taking so long?
- 来吧，已经。
- 什么事要花这么长时间？
[items crashing]
[物品崩溃]
- Aah.
Oh.
- 啊啊。
哦。
Oh.
Aww, that's gonna come out
of my paycheck.
哇哦，这个会出来的
我的薪水。
[grunts]
[咕哝]
- My legs!
- 我的腿！
I'm okay.
我没事。
[oven timer dings]
Slightly less okay.
[烤箱定时器的声音]
少一点还好。
- SpongeBob!
- 海绵宝宝！
- Yeah?
- 是的？
- What are you--whoa,
you've been working out.
- 你是什么——哇，
你一直在锻炼。
- Yeah, I hope you got
some glue for me
- 是的，我希望你能得到
给我一些胶水
because I am ripped!
因为我被撕裂了！
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
[grunts]
[咕哝]
Oh, I'm late for the gym.
哦，我去健身房迟到了。
Can you cover for me
in the kitchen, Squidward?
你能替我掩护吗
在厨房里，章鱼哥？
- Yes.
Anything, you meathead.
- 是的。
什么都行，你这个肉头。
Just go before
you destroy the place.
走之前就行
你毁了这个地方。
[items crashing]
[物品崩溃]
- Larry?
- Ugh.
- 拉里？
- 呃。
- Gee, Larry, you've really
let yourself go.
- 哎呀，拉里，你真的
放手吧。
- With all this paperwork,
- 有了所有这些文书工作，
I haven't had any time
to do my crunches.
我还没有时间
做仰卧起坐。
The only thing I've been
crunching is numbers.
我唯一做过的事
运算就是数字。
But I'm gonna get back in shape.
You'll see.
但我会恢复体形的。
你会看到的。
- Yeah, Larry, sure you will.
- 是的，拉里，你当然会的。
- SpongeBob,
tell me the truth.
- 海绵宝宝，
告诉我真相。
Do I have a potbelly?
我有大肚腩吗？
- I--no, Larry,
don't be silly.
- 我——不，拉里，
别傻了。
You don't have a potbelly.
你没有大肚腩。
- Ugh.
- 呃。
See you in exercise class,
I guess.
运动课上见
我猜。
[sobbing]
[抽泣]
- Oh, boy!
Free soup!
- 哦，孩子！
免费汤！
[slurps]
Little heavy on the salt.
[啜饮]
盐有点重。
[all muttering]
[大家嘀咕]
- Oh, he'll be here.
Don't worry.
- 哦，他会在这里。
不用担心。
Larry made me
the man I am today.
拉里让我
今天的我。
- Oh, look at that.
- Oh, wow.
- 哦，看看那个。
- 哦，哇。
- He taught me
just do stuff you always do
- 他教我的
做你经常做的事情
but do it on your back.
但要在背上做。
Laugh on your back.
笑在你的背上。
[laughing]
[笑]
[all laughing]
[全都笑了]
Walk on your back.
背着走。
[all grunting]
[全都咕哝]
And don't forget,
always be hydrating.
并且不要忘记，
始终保持保湿。
That means
drink plenty of water.
这意味着
多喝水。
all:
Ah.
全部：
啊。
- I hope Larry's okay.
- 我希望拉里没事。
While we're waiting,
当我们等待的时候，
I guess we can ride bicycles
on our backs.
我想我们可以骑自行车
在我们的背上。
[all grunting and groaning]
[所有的咕哝声和呻吟声]
- Hmm.
[moaning]
- 唔。
[呻吟]
- Hey, Larry, thanks for
all the free steam.
- 嘿，拉里，谢谢你
所有的自由蒸汽。
[laughs]
Sucker.
[笑]
傻瓜。
- [sighs]
- [叹气]
[groaning]
[呻吟]
Oh, what's the use?
哦，那有什么用呢？
[breathing heavily]
[呼吸粗重]
Ah, who am I kidding?
啊，我在跟谁开玩笑呢？
- You wanted to see me, sir?
- 你想见我吗，先生？
- Yeah, look, uh,
you're obviously
- 是的，看，呃，
你显然是
the alpha male
at the gym now,
雄性领袖
现在在健身房，
and I'm just a shell
of my former self.
而我只是一个躯壳
以前的我。
- I hear ya, Larry.
- 我听到了，拉里。
I just want to get back
to the Krusty--
我只想回来
致库斯蒂——
- I need you
to take over.
- 我需要你
接管。
You're a natural leader,
SpongeBob.
你是天生的领导者
海绵宝宝。
You should be in charge
of the fun stuff
你应该负责
有趣的事情
while I sit here
in the reception area
当我坐在这里时
在接待区
slowly getting fatter
and paler until I die.
慢慢变胖
直到我死为止，脸色都变得苍白。
- It sounds great.
- 听起来很棒。
- [crying]
- [哭泣]
- Oh, Larry, look at me.
- 哦，拉里，看着我。
I'm too big
to work the grill anymore.
我太大了
不再在烤架上工作了。
That makes me sad.
这让我很难过。
- Come over here
and give me a bro hug.
- 过来这里
给我一个兄弟般的拥抱。
- You mean a "brug"?
- 你的意思是“布鲁格”？
- I don't wanna
call it that.
- 我不想
就这么称呼吧。
- Here's to our new lives.
- 为我们的新生活干杯。
Our terrible,
terrible, new lives.
我们可怕的，
可怕的新生命。
[both crying]
[两人都哭了]
Oh, whoa, what happened?
哦，哇，发生了什么事？
- Dude, you were
just over hydrated.
- 伙计，你是
只是水分过多。
Those weren't real muscles.
那些不是真正的肌肉。
They were water muscles.
他们是水肌。
- Larry, your "brug"
was so super strong,
- 拉里，你的“布鲁格”
是如此的超级强大，
it took the water muscles
right out of me.
它消耗了水肌肉
就在我身边。
- Don't say "brug."
- 不要说“布鲁格”。
- [laughs]
Brug.
- [笑]
布鲁格。
[both laughing]
[两人都笑了]
- SpongeBob, laughing on my back
was just what I needed.
- 海绵宝宝，在我背上笑
这正是我所需要的。
You're a pretty good
instructor after all.
你是一个很不错的人
毕竟是导师。
Oh, boy, the way you laugh
really gets on my nerves.
哦，男孩，你笑起来的样子
真让我心烦意乱。
- [laughing]
- [笑]
- The very next evening...
- 就在第二天晚上...
- [humming]
- [嗡嗡声]
- Well, that was the last
customer, SpongeBob.
- 嗯，那是最后一次
顾客，海绵宝宝。
- Oh, what a great day.
- 哦，多么美好的一天啊。
- And you know why
it was a great day?
- 你知道为什么
这是美好的一天吗？
Because Krabs never even
showed up.
因为螃蟹从来没有
出现了。
- Huh?
[sniffing]
- 啊？
[嗅嗅]
What is that smell?
那是什么气味？
Mr. Krabs, how long
have you been in there?
蟹老板，多久了
你去过那里吗？
- I think I'm done.
- 我想我已经完成了。
Would you mind rubbing
a little butter on me?
你介意擦吗
我身上有一点黄油吗？
[mellow tropical music]
【柔和的热带音乐】
* *
**